You listen to me
There is a person
He drinks Coke every day
Often eat hamburgers and fries
Do you know what happened?
Blood sugar is normal
No fatty liver
Who is this person?
He's not the chosen one.
He is President Trump of the United States
Hu Naiwen starts his lecture
I am your old friend, Doctor Hu
I want to share this episode with you
1.He drank 12 cans of Coke and used one trick to keep his blood sugar normal
2.What to do when blood sugar levels soar? 2 acupuncture points to lower blood sugar
3.One type of exercise has a great effect, reducing blood sugar by 22%
4.Natural insulin assists! Drink 1 tea to stabilize blood sugar
5.Sleeping less than this amount doubles your risk of diabetes
He drank 12 cans of Coke and used one trick to keep his blood sugar normal
Drink Coke every day
drank 12 cans of Coke all day.
A dozen
This person is the President of the United States, Trump
Trump
He also drinks Coke as water
What about him?
also love fast food restaurants.
Hey, eat like this every day
blood sugar level would probably skyrocket.
didn't expect his blood sugar
It's normal
Hey, why is this?
Because the cola
he drinks has no sugar
like sugar-free cola
It's sugar-free
drink sugar-free cola
Won't blood sugar spike?
Right
Some netizens actually tested it and said
He is at 12 noon
drank a bottle of sugar-free cola.
The blood sugar level
did not rise or fall significantly
in 4 hours
It's still
in a level state.
Sugar-free cola uses a sugar substitute
For example
Aspartame
This artificial sweetener
No calories
So blood sugar won't spike
in a short time.
But remind you
of one thing.
Although sugar-free cola
Little effect on blood sugar
can't drink it every day.
There are two major problems
if you drink it every day
First, in the long run
May interfere with blood sugar regulation
Second, artificial sweeteners
It will stimulate your appetite
You will eat more
without realizing it
Causes blood sugar to rise again
For your health
Don't drink Coke
every day.
Is it because Trump has a special physique?
There are still health blind spots that
I don't know about.
Trump did one thing right
He's not on medicine.
But by losing weight
You know Trump
How many kilograms lose?
Not 1kg or 5kg
At least he lost
9 kg
There are studies that prove that
Just lose 5-10% of your body weight
can lower blood sugar levels
Reduce reliance on medication
so
Blood sugar can be controlled
I will share with you
More ways to improve the three highs
Haven't subscribed to my channel yet
Please like and subscribe
Hey, thank you.
What to do when blood sugar is skyrocketing? Press 2 acupoints to lower blood sugar
Here are two acupuncture points to teach you how to press
One acupoint to lower blood sugar
Another acupoint for the spleen and stomach
Let you digest smoothly
Endocrine is also well regulated
These two acupoints are
Zú sān lǐacupoint (Transliteration)Shǎo hǎiacupoint (Transliteration)
Sān lǐacupoint (Transliteration)is also calledZú sān lǐacupoint (Transliteration)
Because it's on the foot
Where is theZú sān lǐacupoint (Transliteration)located?
It's below the knee
below the outer knee
About four fingers long
You can press your left and right feet for 3 minutes
Press once in the morning and evening
What are the benefits of this acupuncture point?
People with high blood sugar
Often the spleen and stomach are not good
Digestive function becomes poor
PressZú sān lǐacupoint (Transliteration)
Strengthens the spleen and replenishes Qi
Nutrition for you to eat
Able to absorb well
Natural blood sugar is stable
TheZú sān lǐacupoint (Transliteration)just introduced
Is it comfortable to press?
Next, press the second acupoint.
Shǎo hǎiacupoint (Transliteration)
You bend your elbows.
There is a depression on the inside of the elbow
This place is calledShǎo hǎiacupoint (Transliteration)
Draw circles with your thumb
Rub it like this
How to know
Did you press it correctly?
When you press
There is a sour and numb feeling
That's the right one.
Who is suitable for pressing
The kind of person
whose blood sugar levels go up when they are nervous
Press to
stabilize blood sugar
No loss of control
One type of exercise has a great effect, reducing blood sugar by 22%
The acupuncture points just mentioned
You can do it by sitting quietly.
Very suitable for introverts
People who like to stay at home
The editor says this is called
Type I
If you are a lively person
want to move after eating
Go out for some fresh air
Type E
This one is perfect for you.
Eat and walk for ten minutes
According to New Zealand
Research at the University of Otago
People with type 2 diabetes
After eating
Brisk walking for 10 minutes
After three meals a day
Walk for ten minutes each
and take a brisk walk after dinner
Better results
Blood sugar can be lowered to
22%
Yes
You often say that people with high blood sugar
The easiest way to lower blood sugar
Just sports
No need to spend a dime
Even the medical expenses are saved
It's a good deal
certainly
I would recommend you to brisk walking
Just like taking blood sugar lowering medicine
Affordable and useful
Does anyone
in your family have type 2 diabetes?
Their insulin function is poor
Sit down and watch TV after eating
Just take a breath there
The body isn't moving.
In this case
Blood sugar easily gets stuck in the blood
Don't move
Poor blood circulation
What to do in this case
After a meal
Get up and walk around. Move around.
Cells of the body
will consume some energy
Right?
At this time
Cells need to
absorb the blood sugar
Replenish energy
Blood sugar will not accumulate
in the blood vessels
To stabilize
blood sugar
I'll tell you again
Exercise
Natural insulin assists! Drink 1 tea to stabilize blood sugar
After a meal
Fear of high blood sugar
Come drink this cup of tea
Keep your blood sugar stable
Mountain Bitter Melon Tea
Drinking is simple
On the market
There are bags of bitter melon for sale
Sliced
After you buy it
and eat your fill
Get a mug
This mountain bitter gourd
Put two or three pieces
Pour hot water again
Then simmer for ten minutes
Ten minutes have passed
Drink it
Blood sugar is stable
can also remove greasiness
It's really great
Research has found that
bitter melon contains an ingredient called
Momordicoside
It's like
Like natural insulin
Stimulates pancreatic β cells
to secrete insulin
Slowly lower blood sugar
I have a patient
He once told me
In addition to taking medicine to control blood sugar,
It is also used with bitter melon for maintenance
How did he do it?
I'll also tell you secretly
He said he ate the Gooseberry
He drank bitter melon tea
While eating this Gooseberry
His blood sugar was under control
very quickly.
Dear sugar friends, you can try it
Remember bitter melon
It helps control blood sugar
I didn't ask you to stop taking the medicine.
To stabilize blood sugar
still need a balanced diet
Exercise, follow the doctor's instructions
Overall conditioning will be effective
Are there any taboos?
have
Mountain bitter melon is hán (Transliteration)
You have a xū hán (Transliteration) constitution and a weak spleen and stomach.
don't recommend you drink it every day.
Drink too much
might even have diarrhea.
stomach is not feeling well either.
Buy dried bitter melon
There are two types: sun drying and drying
So which one is better to buy?
I would recommend you to sunbathe.
Saponins in bitter melon
polyphenols and these kinds of compounds
Afraid of high temperature
Sun drying or low temperature drying
Can be preserved more completely
It tastes better when you drink it.
have a sugar friend
He drinks apple cider vinegar to lower his blood sugar
Is this effective?
You can drink apple cider vinegar
Can buy
Sugar-free, simple ingredients
Delays stomach emptying
Your stomach won't be so upset.
And stabilize blood sugar
People with sensitive stomachs, be careful.
You are not fit to drink.
Drinking it will stimulate stomach acid
Sleeping less than this amount doubles your risk of diabetes
You try very hard to control your diet
Exercise every day
Blood sugar won't go down
What’s the purpose after all
You may have overlooked the most important thing.
Sleep
Not getting enough sleep
It not only damages the kidneys and liver
According to a study
in the Journal of the American Heart Association
There is a sleep psychologist in the United States
He tracked more than 1,600 people
Nearly 30 years
turn out
Originally there
People who already have high blood pressureor diabetes
If sleep less than 6 hours a day
Risk of dying from a heart attack or stroke
Will increase by two times
The most terrifying thing is
If these people also have cancer
The death rate will triple
Poor sleep
Why does it affect blood sugar?
You don't get enough sleep
The body secretes
More stress hormones
It's called cortisol
Cortisol rises
The effect of insulin
will be suppressed
Blood sugar is difficult
Absorbed by cells
The result is blood sugar
Will get higher and higher
I don't have diabetes
Sometimes I stay up late to watch a TV series
It's okay to sleep less
the editor
Healthy people sleep too little
Healthy people will also have high blood sugar
if they sleep too little
Waking up more than two or three times during the night
Or when you wake up in the morning and still feel
Ouch, I'm so tired.
These poor sleep quality conditions
It more than doubles
your risk of
developing type 2 diabetes
But don't just look at
your high blood sugar
immediately scared myself
Go to the Endocrinology
Now everyone thinks that high blood sugar
is caused by insulin problems
No
High blood sugar may also
be a thyroid problem.
It could be an adrenal gland problem.
Cold, nervous, etc.
There are also emotional issues
Even problems related to
spleen function
The point is
You can't
Just lower your blood sugar.
But to find
Causes of high blood sugar
Solving the root problem is helpful
Starting from tonight
Sleep well
It is the first step to stabilize your blood sugar
Friends who like this video
Please click the super thank you button below the video
Give us support